beyondretro.com 2019-01-05

# Privacy Policy – Beyond Retro

### ****

### ****

## PRIVACY

The purpose of this statement is to tell you what Personal Information we collect about you during your visit to this Website and what we do with that information. Your visit to www.beyondretro.com and the sale of our goods to you via www.beyondretro.com are subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions.

Beyond Retro.com ("Beyond Retro") is committed to protecting the privacy of our site visitors and customers. The Beyond Retro team members are customers themselves of other Internet sites and fully appreciate and respect the importance of privacy on the Internet. We will not disclose information about our customers to third parties except where we have your express permission to do so as part of providing a service to you - e.g. arranging for a product to be sent to you, carrying out credit and other security checks and for the purposes of customer research.

**Cookies**

Please refer to our [Cookie Policy](https://www.beyondretro.com/pages/cookie-policy)

**Collection of Information**

We do not collect Personal Information about you, except when you provide it to us. When you submit your Personal Information on [www.beyondretro.com](https://www.beyondretro.com/), you will be asked to consent to the processing and transfers of your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. If you would prefer that we don’t collect any Personal Information from you, please do not provide us with any such information.

Except as otherwise disclosed in this Privacy Policy, we will use the Personal Information you provide us through www.beyondretro.com only for the purposes of processing your orders and responding to any comments or questions you have.

We collect information in a number of ways:

  * When you register for an account or make a purchase via beyondretro.com
  * When you make a purchase at one of our Beyond Retro stores.
  * When you contact Beyond Retro by telephone, email or post.
  * When you enter and prize drawer or competition run or hosted by Beyond Retro
  * When you complete any surveys hosted or managed by Beyond Retro
  * When you register for the Beyond Retro loyalty scheme, Beyond Retro Loyalty Points.
  * When applying for employment at Beyond Retro
  * When you visit our website: we use cookies to improve the experience of shopping on the Beyond Retro website and to help us understand our aggregate customer data. Please refer to our [Cookie Policy](https://www.beyondretro.com/pages/cookie-policy) for more information.  

We may use the information you provide in aggregate (non-personally identifiable) form for internal business purposes, such as generating statistics and developing marketing plans. We may collect, store or accumulate certain non-personally identifiable information concerning your use of www.beyondretro.com, such as information regarding which of our pages are most popular and general website administration.

We may use your information collected from the website to personalise your repeat visits to the website.

**Sharing of information**

We will not sell your name, address, e-mail address, credit card information or personal information to any third party (excluding partners from whom you may have linked to our site) without your expressed permission.

We may disclose any information, including Personal Information, we deem necessary, in our sole discretion, to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request.

**Sensitive information and accuracy**

Sensitive information is not sought through this website. Sensitive information includes data relating to: race or ethnic origin; political opinions; religious or other similar beliefs; physical or mental health. If you do provide sensitive information, by providing that information you explicitly consent to us using it for the purposes for which it has been provided.

We will take reasonable steps to create an accurate record of any Personal Information you have submitted through the Website. However, we do not assume responsibility for confirming the ongoing accuracy of your Personal Information. If you advise us that your Personal Information is no longer accurate, we will so far as practicable, make corrections. If any of the information that you provided on registration changes, please update your records immediately by visiting the "My Account" page or by [contacting us.](https://www.beyondretro.com/pages/contact-us)

**Marketing communications**

With your express permission, we may also use your information to tell you about our products, promotions and special offers that may be of interest to you, by email, mail or by telephone. In particular, we may look at what you have previously ordered in an attempt to tell you about promotions that will be of particular interest to you. 

You will only receive information from us such as Newsletters if you sign up to receive this information via our website, in one of our stores or via one of our owned communications, such as a connected social media account, prize draw promotion or similar. 

**How can I unsubscribe from marketing communications?**

At anytime you can request that your details be removed from our mailing list.

All customers are given the opportunity to opt-out of receiving such further information that they give. However, this decision may be reversed at any time by updating your profile in the "My Account" page or by contacting customer services at customercare@beyondretro.com

You can opt-out by visiting "Your Details" in "My Account" on the Beyond Retro website. You can access "My Account" once you register and login. You can also click on the "unsubscribe" link in any email communications which we might send you.

**How long do we keep hold of your information?**

We keep your personal information for as long as is required to provide our agreed or contracted service to you. This can vary depending on whether you have purchased something from the Beyond Retro website or if we are providing ongoing customer care for example. In some circumstances, we may be required to keep customer data for legal, regulatory or insurance purposes. We will not keep customer data for longer than required. You can ask us to delete or remove your Personal Information in some circumstances such as where we no longer need it or if you withdraw your consent (where applicable). 

**How do we keep your information secure?**

We take steps to ensure your personal information is kept secure and confidential and protected from loss, alteration, corruption, theft or misuse. All Beyond Retro employees are committed to respecting the confidentiality of our customers’ Personal Information by contract. 

We implement various security measures to protect the security of your Personal Information, both on line and off line. Your Personal Information will be stored at facilities located across the world and not necessarily within the EEA. If you have any questions about security at our Website, Please get in [contact.](https://www.beyondretro.com/pages/contact-us)

**Site Statistics and Analysis**

We may disclose aggregate, anonymous statistics about the number of visitors to this Website or number of purchases made. Both the cookies and the embedded code provide statistical information about visits to pages on the site, the duration of individual page view, paths taken by visitors through the site, data on visitors' screen settings and other general information. Beyond Retro uses and stores this type of information, as with that obtained from other cookies used on the site, to help it improve the services to its customers. Further information regarding the way in which this information is obtained and used can be obtained by [contacting us.](https://www.beyondretro.com/pages/contact-us)

You can always update or change your Account information including your password on our site by logging into the “My Account” section of our web site.

We would strongly recommend that you do not use the browser's password memory function as that would permit other people using your terminal to access your personal information.

**Third Parties**

We may retain other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf in relation to the purposes set forth in this Privacy Policy. Examples include credit/debit card validation and authorisation agencies, data analysis firms, customer support specialists and webhosting companies. Such third parties may be provided with access to your Personal Information only with your express permission, if needed to perform their functions, but may not use such information for any other purpose. Such third parties may be located in countries both inside and outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). Although countries outside the EEA may not require the same level of protection of Personal Information as countries within the EEA, we always demand that third parties adhere to the same procedures that we follow ourselves with respect to your Personal Information, including this Privacy Policy.

**Links**

This Website may contain links to or from other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. This Privacy Policy applies only to the information we collect on this Website. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of other websites you link to from our Website or otherwise visit.

**Business Transfers**

As we continue to develop our business, we might sell certain of our assets or be sold. In such transactions, user information, including Personal Information, generally is one of the transferred business assets, and by submitting your Personal Information on the Website you agree that your Personal Information may be transferred to such parties in these circumstances.

**Notification of changes**

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post the revised policy here. As we may make changes at any time without notifying you, we suggest that you periodically consult this Privacy Policy. Please note that our rights to use your Personal Information will be based on the Privacy Policy in effect at the time the information is used. If the preceding sentence is deemed to violate applicable law, the Privacy Policy in effect at the time your Personal Information was collected will apply.

**Data Controller & Rights of Access**

The personal information you provide to us will be managed by the Ecommerce Business Manager. This Privacy Policy shall be construed in accordance with the laws of England and Wales.

Beyond Retro is the data controller for the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the Act).

**Right of access**

You have the right to access the information which Beyond Retro holds about you and your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. You can ask us to delete or remove your personal information in some circumstances such as where we no longer need it or if you withdraw your consent (where applicable). 

**Contacting Us**

We are always pleased to hear from our customers (even if it is a complaint!). We are always grateful for any time you spend providing us with the knowledge we need to ensure our customers are completely satisfied - we want you to return to the site and to recommend us to your friends and family. If you have any questions or feedback about this statement, or if you would like us to stop processing your information, please do not hesitate to contact a member of our Customer Care team at Beyond Retro team [contact](https://www.beyondretro.com/pages/contact-us), who will be delighted to answer any questions you may have.

Last updated: 26-05-18
